<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Halifax Info</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="open_kijiji">Open Kijiji</string>
    <string name="open_airbnb">OPEN AIRBNB</string>
    <string name="accomodation_details">Accomodation Details</string>
    <string name="about">About:-

The only helpful/descriptive app out there for the students landing in halifax with an aim of living the Dal Life. If you are a student coming to
Halifax and dont have any idea of what your supposed to do before stepping into Dalhousie student life, then you hav chosen just the
right app for help. All you need to do is to go through the options provided within the application and choose the one related to topic you have a doubt
about. Once you make a choice, you will be redirected to all the information you need to have about that topic before/after landing in Halifax
and voila ! you are good to go.

The application in general is useful for all the students looking for the information on how to find accomodtaion, means of transportation etc. It more
specifically targets the Dalhousie students whne it comes to information about what tasks a newly accepted to accomplish before going formward with studies.
The application has been designed in the simplest manner possible and will be easy to understand and use, for all the first time users. If in case you  still
have any doubt roaming around in your head, feel free to visit our FAQ section to get some additional/useful information.

							Handcrafted By Your Fellow Dal Students With Love !!!!</string>

    <string name="faq">Q 1) What happens at the airport ?
-> Remember to bring all your documents with you including, Letter Of Acceptance, GIC certificate, Transcripts of previous schools attended and ofcourse your
passport. Present all the documents demanded by the immigration officer. Once satisfied, he/she will issue you your study permit.

Q 2) How can I activate my GIC account?
-> Go to any nearby branch of the bank in which you have applied for GIC account. Take your passport, study permit and  University issued Letter
Of Acceptance. Ask any of the employees attending you to activate the account and they will take care of the rest.

Q 3) Where can I get my student ID ?
-> You need to go to DalCard Office located at coberg Road. You need to have a valid government-issued photo ID with you.

Q 4) Where can I get my Bus Pass ?
-> As a student you need not get one. You will be using your Dalhousie ID as Bus Pass.

Q5) Where can I get my SIN number ?
-> Go to Service Canada with a valid government-issued photo ID and get your SIN number made. You will need to tell them the address the place
you are currently living in along with the postal code.

Q6) Can I work On and Off campus ?
-> Generally you can but it is advised to consult the international student advisor in the university about it.

Q7) How many hours am I allowed to work ?
-> 20 hours/week during study time and upto 40 hours/weel during study break.

Q8) Where can I get the books required for my course ?
-> Killiam library is the place to go. Its located near Henry Hicks building.

</string>
</resources>
